Dutch Van Der Linde

General Web Developer Baghdad

I am a software engineer who specializes in cross-platform development using React and Javascript i have successfully identified and resolved complex issues, often working collaboratively with team members to develop creative solutions that deliver results.

Also proficient in Android Apps development using Android Studio.

dutchvanderlinde@gmail.com

+12391617000



Dutch

dutcvander.com

Video Games

Reading

Traveling

Experience

Local Company

November 2021 - March 2023 (1 year 5 months) Web Developer (Iraq, Baghdad)

Freelance

Feb 2020 - 2023 (3 Years)

Web Developer (Iraq, Baghdad)

Education

Master's Degree in Software Enginering

August 2020 - December 2021 Amercan Univirsty, Iraq, Baghdad.

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

August 2016 - June 2020

BLAH BLAH BLAHU University, Iraq, Baghdad.

<>> Projects

Syntho

React Native + Web

Cross platform electronic music education application.

IDK

React Native

Mobile app BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH

React Apps

React

Fast # and easy beautiful progressive websites and apps

Voice Contorl App

React

An app used to control smart home fetures

Soft Skills

Quick learner and problem solver

Responsible, punctual and result oriented

Good English speaking and reading

Hard Skills



Languages

Arabic: Native

English: Superior

French: Intermediate